<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Totality</title>
    <link>https://str8d8a.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Totality</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://str8d8a.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Facility</title>
      <link>https://str8d8a.github.io/docs/concepts/ontology/facility/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://str8d8a.github.io/docs/concepts/ontology/facility/</guid>
      <description>Facility A facility is any structure or location that is constructed and/or largely managed by human effort. Facilities are described in terms of the materials they house, the transformations they perform on those materials, and/or the services they provide.
   Facility Transformations Stocks Services     Mine In-ground ore (resource) ⇒ refined ore (reservoir) On-site inventory Employment   Dam  Water reservoir Electricity provisioning, Water provisioning, Recreation   Clothing factory Textiles ⇒ finished clothing Input inventory Employment   Hospital  Beds Personal    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reservoir</title>
      <link>https://str8d8a.github.io/docs/concepts/ontology/reservoir/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://str8d8a.github.io/docs/concepts/ontology/reservoir/</guid>
      <description>Reservoirs </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Motivation</title>
      <link>https://str8d8a.github.io/docs/motivation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://str8d8a.github.io/docs/motivation/</guid>
      <description>Becoming Planetary Thinkers As a civilization, we need to make a leap.
 The idea that there is a human economy separate from or above the rest of the planet, apart from nature, is simply wrong; it has also been incredibly destructive. Humans have made from the elements and energy around us many wonderful new things (and some horrific ones as well); but, even so, the entirety of the human economy is contained within the natural world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Process</title>
      <link>https://str8d8a.github.io/docs/concepts/ontology/process/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://str8d8a.github.io/docs/concepts/ontology/process/</guid>
      <description>Processes A process refers to any naturally occurring physical, chemical, or biological transformation. The inclusion of natural processes alongside human activities is a clear indication of the fact that Totality aims to model the human and environmental layers of the planetary system as one, without rendering either sphere as subordinate to the other or &amp;ldquo;external&amp;rdquo;.
At the same time, and in contrast to the other node types - facilities, reservoirs, and resources - Totality makes no attempt to capture or describe all of the natural processes on the planet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resource</title>
      <link>https://str8d8a.github.io/docs/concepts/ontology/resource/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://str8d8a.github.io/docs/concepts/ontology/resource/</guid>
      <description>Resources </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Routes and Conveyances</title>
      <link>https://str8d8a.github.io/docs/concepts/ontology/routes-and-conveyances/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://str8d8a.github.io/docs/concepts/ontology/routes-and-conveyances/</guid>
      <description>Routes and Conveyances The four node types describe the stocks (reservoirs, resources) and transformations (facilities, processes) of materials, animals, and people, as well as the services they provide through their operation and being.
But matter and energy of all kinds must move from one place to another in order for the planetary system to function. These movements are both a consequence of natural processes and intentional human activity, and Totality is concerned with both of these categories.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>